



314-574-2566



santiagoestebancmc@gmail.com



Bogotá D.C



santicarreno13

SKILLS

- Spring Boot JAVA
- Laravel PHP
- JavaScript
- Vue, NodeJS
- MSQL
- CSS-SASS
- GIT

SANTIAGO CARREÑO

DEVELOPER OF SOFWARE

I am a qualified and professional web developer with four years of experience in database administration and website design. Strong creative and analytical skills. My main objective is to provide my best knowledge and to be able to learn, know and understand everything that is available to me to do.

EXPERIENCE

DEVELOPER WEB

ACCEDO S.A.S

2023 - Present

- The development of logic models to facilitate optimal management of the application
- Development of components for correct operation

ANALYSIS CONTENT

SENA

2020 - 2023

- Database administration and website design.
- Developed the logic for an optimized platform of an information system for a parking lot and a cafeteria

EDUCATION

ACADEMIC BACHELOR

Alberto Lleras Camargo school

2016 - 2021

TECHNICIAN IN ANALYSIS AND DESIGN OF INFORMATION SYSTEMS

SENA

2020 - 2021

TECHNOLOGIST IN ANALYSIS AND DESIGN OF INFORMATION SYSTEMS

SENA

2022 - 2023